<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>KCDNUG on Duane Newman</title>
    <link>https://duanenewman.net/tags/kcdnug/</link>
    <description>Recent content in KCDNUG on Duane Newman</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>Duane Newman (Duane Newman)</managingEditor>
    <copyright>Copyright Duane Newman</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2015 22:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://duanenewman.net/tags/kcdnug/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>KCDNUG Last Minute Speaking (or, the perils of running a user group)</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/kcdnug-last-minute-speaking-or-the-perils-of-running-a-user-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2015 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/kcdnug-last-minute-speaking-or-the-perils-of-running-a-user-group/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;What a crazy user group meeting tonight. Through some schedule mix-ups (partly due to having things scheduled too far in advance and not following up) we ended up with no sponsor and no speaker.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;I was originally not going to make it to tonight’s meeting due to some schedule conflicts, but they cleared up at the last minute so I joined Brent to help run the meeting. When we go there we discovered that due to schedule conflicts they had we were in a different room, so we got busy redirecting everyone to the new room. After a while we started wondering where the scheduled sponsor was... Then we also started wondering where the speaker was. We soon learned the sponsor didn&#39;t realize they were scheduled for tonight and would not be there, so Brent got on the phone and Alien Arc became the new sponsor. When it was just a few minutes from go-time and still no speaker (didn&#39;t have contact info) it became apparent that one of us was going to speak.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
      <category>speaking</category>
      
      <category>Community</category>
      
      <category>KCDNUG</category>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>