<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>HDC on Duane Newman</title>
    <link>https://duanenewman.net/tags/hdc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in HDC on Duane Newman</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>Duane Newman (Duane Newman)</managingEditor>
    <copyright>Copyright Duane Newman</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2015 11:45:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://duanenewman.net/tags/hdc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Heartland Developers Conference 2015</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/heartland-developers-conference-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2015 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/heartland-developers-conference-2015/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This was my first year speaking at the Heartland Developers Conference in Omaha, although I’ve attended many times through the years as an attendee. The experience was quite a lot of fun, and I had a good time hanging out with old friends and making a few new ones. My wife came with me and good time watching all of us “geeks” hangout. &lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;This was the first time doing a new talk, and the first talk that didn’t involve any demo’s, and it was not scheduled until Friday morning. Needless to say I spent a lot of time fretting about the talk and was constantly tweaking my slides. The talk itself went really well, the audience was very involved with a lot of great questions. My talk was on DevOps and I brought to light the importance and advantages of getting a DevOps friendly environment established. I was happy to see I had a mix of developers, IT guys and managers as I really tried to target the talk to a broad audience. All-in-all I’m looking forward to what HDC might bring next year.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
      <category>agile</category>
      
      <category>DevOps</category>
      
      <category>Community</category>
      
      <category>Speaking</category>
      
      <category>HDC</category>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>