<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Vegas on Duane Newman</title>
    <link>https://duanenewman.net/tags/vegas/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Vegas on Duane Newman</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>Duane Newman (Duane Newman)</managingEditor>
    <copyright>Copyright Duane Newman</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2016 11:46:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://duanenewman.net/tags/vegas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Bluff v1.1 hot off the presses</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/bluff-v11-hot-off-the-presses/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2016 11:46:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/bluff-v11-hot-off-the-presses/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I had a little time today to work on Bluff, my extension for Sony Vegas Pro. Over the last couple weeks I’ve done several things to the project, including:&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;ul&gt;   &lt;li&gt;Converting the project to .NET 3.5 (from 2.0) &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Converting the UI to WPF (still a little cleanup to do on that UI, but it is a lot easier to work with now) &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Add a new command called &lt;em&gt;Arrange Events By Created Timestamp&lt;/em&gt; that spaces the events out on the timeline relative to each others created timestamp &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Changed the Vegas DLL reference to a v8 dll (to provide better compatibility form Vegas Pro 8 – 13) &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;And last, but not least, I added a WIX based installer to the project &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;  &lt;p&gt;If you just want grab the latest version jump over to the GitHub release page.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
      <category>Bluff</category>
      
      <category>Coding</category>
      
      <category>OSS</category>
      
      <category>plugin</category>
      
      <category>vegas</category>
      
      <category>video</category>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bluff: An OSS Extension for Sony Vegas Pro</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/bluff-oss-extension-for-sony-vegas-pro/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/bluff-oss-extension-for-sony-vegas-pro/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Yesterday, my business Alien Arc Technologies, LLC &lt;a title=&#34;Alien Arc Technologies, LLC Announces Bluff, an OSS Project for Sony Vegas Pro&#34; href=&#34;http://alienarc.com/post/announcing-new-oss-project-bluff-for-vegas-pro-12&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;announced&lt;/a&gt; the release of version 1.0 of an open source project I’ve been tinkering on recently, called Bluff. This is my first OSS project and I’m excited to have created something that I hope others will find useful, and better yet, will contribute their own ideas to.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;h3&gt;History&lt;/h3&gt;  &lt;p&gt;The project came out of my own personal needs and interest. In 2015 I was introduced to the world of scuba diving and I’ve fallen totally in love with it. It didn’t take long before I was combining scuba with my photography hobby.. And suddenly I found I had the perfect environment to do video. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
      <category>OSS</category>
      
      <category>vegas</category>
      
      <category>video</category>
      
      <category>plugin</category>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>