<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Coding on Duane Newman</title>
    <link>https://duanenewman.net/tags/coding/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Coding on Duane Newman</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright Duane Newman</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 May 2016 15:01:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://duanenewman.net/tags/coding/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Nebraska.Code() 2016</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/nebraska-code-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2016 15:01:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/nebraska-code-2016/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Another &lt;a href=&#34;http://nebraskacode.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Nebraska.Code()&lt;/a&gt; is in the books and it was a real blast. The organizers, Adam &amp;amp; Ken, really put in the effort and run a great conference. The other speakers are always quality company and I really enjoyed meeting a few new ones and getting to know some much better. One of the things I enjoy about conference is the circle of friends you make and meet across the country as you travel to this conference and that conference. We had lots of deep, and many more entertaining conversations.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
      <category>Coding</category>
      
      <category>Community</category>
      
      <category>Deployment</category>
      
      <category>mobile</category>
      
      <category>NCC</category>
      
      <category>NebraskaCode</category>
      
      <category>OSS</category>
      
      <category>Speaking</category>
      
      <category>Xamarin</category>
      
      <category>Xamarin Forms</category>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bluff v1.1 hot off the presses</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/bluff-v11-hot-off-the-presses/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2016 11:46:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/bluff-v11-hot-off-the-presses/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I had a little time today to work on Bluff, my extension for Sony Vegas Pro. Over the last couple weeks I’ve done several things to the project, including:&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;ul&gt;   &lt;li&gt;Converting the project to .NET 3.5 (from 2.0) &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Converting the UI to WPF (still a little cleanup to do on that UI, but it is a lot easier to work with now) &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Add a new command called &lt;em&gt;Arrange Events By Created Timestamp&lt;/em&gt; that spaces the events out on the timeline relative to each others created timestamp &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Changed the Vegas DLL reference to a v8 dll (to provide better compatibility form Vegas Pro 8 – 13) &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;And last, but not least, I added a WIX based installer to the project &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;  &lt;p&gt;If you just want grab the latest version jump over to the GitHub release page.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
      <category>Bluff</category>
      
      <category>Coding</category>
      
      <category>OSS</category>
      
      <category>plugin</category>
      
      <category>vegas</category>
      
      <category>video</category>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xamarin Build Errors: Please Install Package Xamarin.Android.Support.v4</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/xamarin-build-errors-please-install-package-xamarinandroidsupportv4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2016 08:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/xamarin-build-errors-please-install-package-xamarinandroidsupportv4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I was out of active Xamarin development for a couple months and recently wanted to jump back in and work on a couple new project ideas. I fired up VS2015 and created a project. It was then that I realized I had not installed the official Xamarin tools since I got my new Surface Book. So I decided it was a good idea to install that latest Xamarin Tools before I did anything else.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
      <category>Xamarin</category>
      
      <category>Xamarin Forms</category>
      
      <category>Coding</category>
      
      <category>Troubleshooting</category>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting your brand’s Twitter timeline in your mobile app</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/getting-your-brands-twitter-timeline-in-your-mobile-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2015 08:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/getting-your-brands-twitter-timeline-in-your-mobile-app/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m working on a demo app to show some simple functionality that can be done with Xamarin Forms. I’m using the opportunity to also make a business card app for myself (and ultimately for &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.alienarc.com&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Alien Arc&lt;/a&gt;). The app has my picture, name, short bio, and other relevant information. This also seemed like a good place to tie in some of my various social network feeds. I quickly added a page that pulls my blog RSS feed and lists my recent posts. That went really quick and next on my list was to load my twitter timeline and show recent tweets. The blog was so easy and quick to do that I thought it would take no time to get twitter integrated.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
      <category>twitter</category>
      
      <category>Xamarin</category>
      
      <category>business</category>
      
      <category>Coding</category>
      
      <category>tips</category>
      
      <category>linq</category>
      
      <category>social</category>
      
      <category>mobile</category>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SkillsUSA Coding Competition</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/skillsusa-coding-competition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2015 12:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/skillsusa-coding-competition/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://duanenewman.net/img/posts/201402-SkillsUSA.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img title=&#34;201402-SkillsUSA&#34; style=&#34;float: right&#34; border=&#34;0&#34; alt=&#34;201402-SkillsUSA&#34; src=&#34;https://duanenewman.net/img/posts/201402-SkillsUSA_thumb.png&#34; width=&#34;244&#34; align=&#34;right&#34; height=&#34;160&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;     &lt;p&gt;On Saturday I had an opportunity to be involved in a SkillsUSA district competition as a judge for the coding competition. I was really impressed with the skill that some of these students (all with less than a year of experience) had. The quality of some of the code they wrote really surprised me.&lt;/p&gt;    &lt;p&gt;It was a really enjoyable experience and I was happy to be able to get more involved in the community with the next generation of coders. I look forward to other opportunities to work with the future of software development and technology.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
      <category>Technology</category>
      
      <category>SkillsUSA</category>
      
      <category>Judging</category>
      
      <category>Coding</category>
      
      <category>Community</category>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>