<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Duane Newman</title>
    <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Duane Newman</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright Duane Newman</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 12:30:00 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://duanenewman.net/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Parallels Shared Network Fails to Connect</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/parallels-shared-network-fails-to-connect/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 12:30:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/parallels-shared-network-fails-to-connect/</guid>
      <description>Today (Monday), out of the blue, one of my Windows 10 Parallels virtual machines decided that it had no connection to the internet. Friday I was on site at a client using thier WiFi network to work through some changes they needed. Today, back at the office, I fired up my VM to push the changes and make a couple more tweaks. I was immediated greated by git telling me that my git host didn&amp;rsquo;t exist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basic Authentication with TFS Package Server</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/2019-07-29-basic-auth-with-tfs-package-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2019 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/2019-07-29-basic-auth-with-tfs-package-server/</guid>
      <description>I recently encountered some authentication issues connecting my Mac to the package service hosted on a client&amp;rsquo;s on-prem TFS server. The server is on a Windows domain and normally I access TFS from a windows VM that is joined to the domain. However, I&amp;rsquo;ve recently found myself on my Mac more often while working on one of thier Xamarin mobile apps. This is when I began having problems.
The Poblem The client has a couple NuGet packages hosted on the TFS server using the Package Management extension, and whenever I tried to do a NuGet restore I would run into authentication errors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Better Way to Override References With PackageReference</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/a-better-way-to-override-references-with-packagereference/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/a-better-way-to-override-references-with-packagereference/</guid>
      <description>Recently, there was a new feature added to msbuild (working in Visual Studio 2019 15.9.9) that generates a variable for each package that contains the full path to the package version being used. All you have to do is add an attribute to each &amp;lt;PackageReference&amp;gt; you want need to work with.
There are just two changes to what we did before:
 Add GeneratePathProperty attribute to &amp;lt;PackageReference&amp;gt; Switch to Pkg&amp;lt;Package_Name&amp;gt; variable in &amp;lt;HintPath&amp;gt;  Step one is pretty simple, add the attribute GeneratePathProperty with a value of true:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forcing a Specific Target Platform With PackageReference</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/forcing-a-specific-target-platform-with-packagereference/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/forcing-a-specific-target-platform-with-packagereference/</guid>
      <description>In my last post about Using Prism with Xamarin.Forms &amp;amp; GTK# I showed how to force the use of .NET Standard reference when using NuGet with packages.config. You may prefer using the &amp;lt;PackageReference&amp;gt; tag in your csproj and found that those changes do not work for your scenario. This post will show you how to achieve the same override with PackageReference based projects.
Using Package Reference If you already have packages installed and are using a packages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Prism With Xamarin.Forms &amp; GTK</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/using-prism-with-xamarin-forms-and-gtk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/using-prism-with-xamarin-forms-and-gtk/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m working on project to replace my car radio with a custom digital dashboard. I&amp;rsquo;m building it on a RaspberryPi and would really like to use Xamarin.Forms and Prism, so I started out with adding a GTK# frontend to my Xamarin.Forms project.
Adding the GTK# Backend Project Before we can add the GTK# project we need to actually install the GTK# libraries. Head over to The Mono Project to download and run the GTK# for .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Running PowerShell Scripts From C#</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/running-powershell-scripts-from-csharp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/running-powershell-scripts-from-csharp/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes the little things can trip up your code, even when you think you are doing all the right things. We recently ran into an issue with a utility that runs an included PowerShell script as part of it operation. When the app was first put into use it seemed to be fine. Recently, it was deployed into a folder with spaces in the name and it began to blow up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Concurrent Reads and Locked Writes with In-Memory Objects</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/concurrent-reads-and-locked-writes-with-in-memory-objects/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/concurrent-reads-and-locked-writes-with-in-memory-objects/</guid>
      <description>The Problem On a recent project one of our clients had implemented an in-memory cache of some high read, low write data. The ultimate solution they had was a List&amp;lt;T&amp;gt; that they could search against while periodically updating when the database was updated. The reads worked great and were incredibly fast. The trouble came when they started to implement the updates. This was in their API layer and so incoming calls were on multiple threads.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indirect connections with Plex and pfSense</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/indirect-connections-with-plex-and-pfsense/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/indirect-connections-with-plex-and-pfsense/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve recently built a custom FreeNAS file server in my house to act as high capacity storage for my personal photos &amp;amp; videos, a Plex Media Server, and an S3 server for offsite backup for my business and family, among a few other minor things. At the same time I also replaced my Ubiquiti EdgeRouter X with a custom pfSense router (primarily for better remote VPN and P2P VPN support).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keeping Observable Collections Up To Date</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/keeping-observable-collections-up-to-date/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/keeping-observable-collections-up-to-date/</guid>
      <description>One of the powerful capabilities we&amp;rsquo;ve learned to leverage when using the MVVM pattern for XAML based apps, whether for the desktop or mobile platforms, is data binding. Binding allows us to easily keep our View up to date with changes in the ViewModel. These bindings are typically pretty quick when not abused, but there are situations where they can become less than performant, causing visual anomalies such as flickering or even impacting general app performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Better Unit Testing with IoC, DI, and Mocking</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/better-unit-testing-with-ioc-di-and-mocking/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/better-unit-testing-with-ioc-di-and-mocking/</guid>
      <description>When you write code designed for dependency injection it can make testing easier.. But it can also make it seem more complex and add a lot of ceremony to creating your testable instances. I thought I would share some tips I use when setting up a new cross-platform mobile project with unit testing. We can take advantage of the same IoC container strategy to make instantiating the class we want to test less painful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First MVP Summit</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/my-first-mvp-summit/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/my-first-mvp-summit/</guid>
      <description>A couple weeks ago I went to my first MVP Summit. The MVP program is a way that Microsoft recognizes &amp;ldquo;technology experts who passionately share their knowledge with the community&amp;rdquo;*. There are several perks to being an MVP. While many may immediately think of the compliemntary MSDN subscription and software licenses from other vendors, I was most excited about the opportunity to go to MVP Summit. As an MVP (under tight NDA) I am able to meet over skype with the various product teams at MS to get a view into where they are headed with thier technologies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teach an old Type new tricks with Extension Methods</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/teach-an-old-type-new-tricks-with-extension-methods/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/teach-an-old-type-new-tricks-with-extension-methods/</guid>
      <description>Extension methods are a great way to add functionality or integration for established types. Learn about some of the cool things that you can do without the need to subclass or modify a class directly. You can even use extension methods to supply specialized functionality that is only relevant in a particular situation or when also making use of another type or library. We&amp;rsquo;ll take a look at a few quick tricks and explore how you can get started with Extension Methods today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All I want for Christmas is a C# Build System</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/all-i-want-for-christmas-is-a-c-sharp-build-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/all-i-want-for-christmas-is-a-c-sharp-build-system/</guid>
      <description>Why So Jolly? This post is part of the The First C# Advent Calendar, celebrating all things C#. After you finish here check out the other great posts in the series.
A C# Build System I&amp;rsquo;ve used many tools over the years to manage builds of large .NET projects including custom BAT/CMD files, customer PowerShell scripts, NAnt, and of course MSBuild. While I&amp;rsquo;ve been happy with the solutions I provided with each of these I&amp;rsquo;ve always found them either awkward to extend or limiting in their extensibility and more recently I needed them to work on a Mac for building Xamarin projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diving in Bonaire - 2016</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/diving-in-bonaire-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2016 14:46:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/diving-in-bonaire-2016/</guid>
      <description>I decided to take a few minutes and reflect on my recent trip to Bonaire and share some accomplishments and observations. To begin with, the flight there is long. We had two options, 45 minute layover to catch an international flight with all our luggage, or 5 hour layover waiting in the airport. We chose the later since no on wanted to miss a flight that only happens once a day and only on Saturday and Sunday each week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Strange Keyboard Layout on Windows 10 Mobile &amp; Lumia 950XL</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/strange-keyboard-layout-on-windows-10-mobile-lumia-950xl/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2016 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/strange-keyboard-layout-on-windows-10-mobile-lumia-950xl/</guid>
      <description>I recently encountered a strange issue with the layout of the keyboard on my Lumia 950XL. This happened after a one of the recent OS updates and it took me a little while researching to figure it out. The issue was that my keyboard was all squashed to the left, instead of taking up the full width of the phone. In addition to that the cursor point was on the right hand side of the keyboard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nebraska.Code() 2016</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/nebraska-code-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2016 15:01:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/nebraska-code-2016/</guid>
      <description>Another Nebraska.Code() is in the books and it was a real blast. The organizers, Adam &amp;amp; Ken, really put in the effort and run a great conference. The other speakers are always quality company and I really enjoyed meeting a few new ones and getting to know some much better. One of the things I enjoy about conference is the circle of friends you make and meet across the country as you travel to this conference and that conference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Build 2016</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/microsoft-build-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/microsoft-build-2016/</guid>
      <description>I hate it when I find a blog post draft that I forgot to post for *weeks*, it’s a little late, but here are some of my impressions from Microsoft’s Build conference this year.
This year&#39;s build was pretty exciting for .NET developers. With strong progress around the Windows platform and major announcements in the mobile developer space. Build was an fun experience and I was able to both reconnect with friends I&#39;ve made on the conference circuit and meet a lot of new faces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Return of Visual Voicemail to the Lumia 950 XL (Dual Sim)</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/the-return-of-visual-voicemail-to-the-lumia-950-xl-dual-sim/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2016 16:58:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/the-return-of-visual-voicemail-to-the-lumia-950-xl-dual-sim/</guid>
      <description>For those that purchased an unlocked Lumia 950 XL from Microsoft in the last few months and have been frustrated at the lack of Visual Voice (that’s everyone who bought one) you can rejoice. Last week I had sketchy WiFi access so I just discovered that I had an update available last night. When I went to take a look at the change log I discovered this little gem:
 Support for Visual Voicemail on Dual SIM phones   It sounds like this has been available in the Windows Insiders build for a little while, but I’ve been hesitant to put my primary phone on the insiders builds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diving the Bay Island of Guanaja, Honduras (Part 5 - Diving)</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/diving-the-bay-island-of-guanaja-honduras-part-5-diving/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2016 11:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/diving-the-bay-island-of-guanaja-honduras-part-5-diving/</guid>
      <description>This is part 5 in a series on scuba travel and our trip to Honduras.
Related Posts
 Diving the Bay Island of Guanaja, Honduras (Part 1 - Packing)  Diving the Bay Island of Guanaja, Honduras (Part 2 - Traveling Photographer)  Diving the Bay Island of Guanaja, Honduras (Part 3 - On the Road)  Diving the Bay Island of Guanaja, Honduras (Part 4 - Lodging)  Diving the Bay Island of Guanaja, Honduras (Part 5 - Diving)   Guanaja Diving The diving in Guanaja is fantastic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diving the Bay Island of Guanaja, Honduras (Part 4 - Lodging)</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/diving-the-bay-island-of-guanaja-honduras-part-4-lodging/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2016 11:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/diving-the-bay-island-of-guanaja-honduras-part-4-lodging/</guid>
      <description>This is part 4 in a series on scuba travel and our trip to Honduras.
Related Posts
 Diving the Bay Island of Guanaja, Honduras (Part 1 - Packing)  Diving the Bay Island of Guanaja, Honduras (Part 2 - Traveling Photographer)  Diving the Bay Island of Guanaja, Honduras (Part 3 - On the Road)  Diving the Bay Island of Guanaja, Honduras (Part 4 - Lodging) Diving the Bay Island of Guanaja, Honduras (Part 5 - Diving)   The Villa   You can read my review of the Villa over on TripAdvisor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diving the Bay Island of Guanaja, Honduras (Part 3 - On the Road)</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/diving-the-bay-island-of-guanaja-honduras-part-3-on-the-road/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 11:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/diving-the-bay-island-of-guanaja-honduras-part-3-on-the-road/</guid>
      <description>This is part 3 in a series on scuba travel and our trip to Honduras.
Related Posts
 Diving the Bay Island of Guanaja, Honduras (Part 1 - Packing)  Diving the Bay Island of Guanaja, Honduras (Part 2 - Traveling Photographer)  Diving the Bay Island of Guanaja, Honduras (Part 3 - On the Road) Diving the Bay Island of Guanaja, Honduras (Part 4 - Lodging)  Diving the Bay Island of Guanaja, Honduras (Part 5 - Diving)   Travel We were traveling from cold weather to warm weather, so we planned ahead and packed shorts in our carry-on so that while we stopped for a layover in Atlanta we could change out of our warmer weather pants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bringing Sight to the Blind (Seeing AI)</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/bringing-sight-to-the-blind-seeing-ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2016 06:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/bringing-sight-to-the-blind-seeing-ai/</guid>
      <description>Perhaps the coolest (and definitely the most heartwarming) announcement at Build today was project Seeing AI. A project spearheaded by Saqib Shaikh, a blind software engineer at Microsoft. This project will enable the blind to “hear” what they are looking at with voice descriptions of the scene in front of them and to be read text (like a menu). This project is a collaboration between Microsoft and Pivothead and will run on both smartphones and the Pivothead smart glasses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diving the Bay Island of Guanaja, Honduras (Part 2 - Traveling Photographer)</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/diving-the-bay-island-of-guanaja-honduras-part-2-traveling-photographer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2016 11:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/diving-the-bay-island-of-guanaja-honduras-part-2-traveling-photographer/</guid>
      <description>Traveling with your photography equipment can be challenging when you are taking all your pictures on dry (or at least solid) ground. Add all the equipment you need if you are going to get wet with you camera and it becomes a production just getting it all to your destination. When I first looked into what to do I had a hard time finding information on what other were doing, so I hope you find this helpful as you plan your underwater photography dive trip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bluff v1.1 hot off the presses</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/bluff-v11-hot-off-the-presses/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2016 11:46:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/bluff-v11-hot-off-the-presses/</guid>
      <description>I had a little time today to work on Bluff, my extension for Sony Vegas Pro. Over the last couple weeks I’ve done several things to the project, including:
 Converting the project to .NET 3.5 (from 2.0)  Converting the UI to WPF (still a little cleanup to do on that UI, but it is a lot easier to work with now)  Add a new command called Arrange Events By Created Timestamp that spaces the events out on the timeline relative to each others created timestamp  Changed the Vegas DLL reference to a v8 dll (to provide better compatibility form Vegas Pro 8 – 13)  And last, but not least, I added a WIX based installer to the project   If you just want grab the latest version jump over to the GitHub release page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merging GoPro Segments Into a Single File</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/merging-gopro-segments-into-a-single-file/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2016 11:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/merging-gopro-segments-into-a-single-file/</guid>
      <description>If you have ever done a long recording with your GoPro you know that you will end up with several ~4GB files instead of a single video file. This can be very inconvenient if you just want to be able to watch the video start to finish, or if you want to apply effects (like de-shaker) across a file boundary.
If you are not familiar with file systems this may seem odd, but it is a well known limitation of the FAT file system which the GoPro, and many other small electronics, use for file storage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diving the Bay Island of Guanaja, Honduras (Part 1 - Packing)</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/diving-the-bay-island-of-guanaja-honduras-part-1-packing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2016 11:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/diving-the-bay-island-of-guanaja-honduras-part-1-packing/</guid>
      <description>This is part 1 in a series on scuba travel and our trip to Honduras.
Related Posts
 Diving the Bay Island of Guanaja, Honduras (Part 1 - Packing) Diving the Bay Island of Guanaja, Honduras (Part 2 - Traveling Photographer)  Diving the Bay Island of Guanaja, Honduras (Part 3 - On the Road)  Diving the Bay Island of Guanaja, Honduras (Part 4 - Lodging)  Diving the Bay Island of Guanaja, Honduras (Part 5 - Diving)   In January my wife and I took our first real scuba diving vacation with our dive shop, The Playground Dive Shop, to the island of Guanaja, Honduras where we stayed and dived with the Villa on Dunbar Rock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Generating Authenticator QR Codes</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/generating-authenticator-qr-codes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2016 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/generating-authenticator-qr-codes/</guid>
      <description>I’ve taken to saving my Authenticator secrets so that I can recover from a lost, damaged or replaced phone with less pain. After actually replacing a phone and having to re-enter all my codes I decided there was a better way then pecking on the phone’s keyboard one letter at a time. I thought that they deliver them to me as a QR code I can scan in the first place, surely I can generate my own to speed up the process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xamarin Build Errors: Please Install Package Xamarin.Android.Support.v4</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/xamarin-build-errors-please-install-package-xamarinandroidsupportv4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2016 08:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/xamarin-build-errors-please-install-package-xamarinandroidsupportv4/</guid>
      <description>I was out of active Xamarin development for a couple months and recently wanted to jump back in and work on a couple new project ideas. I fired up VS2015 and created a project. It was then that I realized I had not installed the official Xamarin tools since I got my new Surface Book. So I decided it was a good idea to install that latest Xamarin Tools before I did anything else.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bluff: An OSS Extension for Sony Vegas Pro</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/bluff-oss-extension-for-sony-vegas-pro/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/bluff-oss-extension-for-sony-vegas-pro/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday, my business Alien Arc Technologies, LLC announced the release of version 1.0 of an open source project I’ve been tinkering on recently, called Bluff. This is my first OSS project and I’m excited to have created something that I hope others will find useful, and better yet, will contribute their own ideas to.
History The project came out of my own personal needs and interest. In 2015 I was introduced to the world of scuba diving and I’ve fallen totally in love with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing Chocolatey behind a corporate proxy</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/installing-chocolatey-behind-a-corporate-proxy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2016 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/installing-chocolatey-behind-a-corporate-proxy/</guid>
      <description>Recently I was working at a project at a new client and needed to add some tools to my development machine. So I turned to one of my favorite tools for getting the apps and tools I need, Chocolatey. The only problem was that I was getting an error installing Chocolatey using the command on their website.
Exception calling &amp;quot;DownloadString&amp;quot; with &amp;quot;1&amp;quot; argument(s): &amp;quot;The remote server returned an error: (407) Proxy Authentication Required.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speaking on DevOps at St. Louis Days of .NET 2015</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/speaking-on-devops-at-st-louis-days-of-net-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2015 09:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/speaking-on-devops-at-st-louis-days-of-net-2015/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;ve been selected to speak at the upcoming St. Louis Days of .NET (STLDODN) on November 12th-14th. I will be presenting my new talk on DevOps, Double Down with DevOps, and am excited about the opportunity to give this topic some attention. Why Speak on DevOps? As a developer I am often frustrated with the amount of manual processes that seem to exist between development and production. Many of us have found ourselves in the situation where we had a single point of failure for a process, the 1 person at the company that knows how to release the new software, or configure the server, or any number of other things that will invariably go wrong when when they are on vacation (or worse, just go on hold).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heartland Developers Conference 2015</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/heartland-developers-conference-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2015 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/heartland-developers-conference-2015/</guid>
      <description>This was my first year speaking at the Heartland Developers Conference in Omaha, although I’ve attended many times through the years as an attendee. The experience was quite a lot of fun, and I had a good time hanging out with old friends and making a few new ones. My wife came with me and good time watching all of us “geeks” hangout. This was the first time doing a new talk, and the first talk that didn’t involve any demo’s, and it was not scheduled until Friday morning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kansas City Developers Conference 2015 Recap</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/kcdc-2015-recap/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2015 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/kcdc-2015-recap/</guid>
      <description>In preparation for my fall conference lineup I thought I would take a minute to reflect on this year’s Kansas City Developers Conference. Once again, I am impressed with the quality of conference that the KCDC crew puts together. Kudos go to Boone, Jon, and Lee for nurturing a small weekend event into what is, today, one of the top conferences in the Midwest for developers (of any discipline). I’ve had the opportunity to go to some of the “BIG” (and expensive) developer conferences out there and experience what they feel like, and to me KCDC has that same polished feel of conferences that cost 10x as much to attend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KCDC 2015 Sessions</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/kcdc-2015-sessions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2015 11:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/kcdc-2015-sessions/</guid>
      <description>KCDC is just a week away and I&#39;m busy updating my materials. I&#39;m looking forward to meeting some great developers and catching up with what is quickly becoming a close group of speaker friends.
I&#39;ll be presenting my Xamarin.Forms talk on Thursday morning at 10:10 AM. Conference mornings are always a little rough, but I like getting the talk done early, then I get to relax, network, and enjoy seeing my friends presenting their talks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interview with STL Tech Talk at STLDODN 2014</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/interview-with-stl-tech-talk-at-stldodn-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2015 08:23:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/interview-with-stl-tech-talk-at-stldodn-2014/</guid>
      <description>Back in November 2014 at the St. Louis Days of .NET conference I sat down with JJ Hammond from STL Tech Talk for an interview. It was a lot of fun and I had a great time talking about Xamarin, Xamarin.Forms, and mobile development for the C# developer. It got lost somewhere among all the other interview videos, but thanks to Kevin and JJ it is was found and is now posted for your viewing pleasure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nebraska.Code() 2015 Retrospect</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/nebraskacode-2015-retrospect/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2015 09:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/nebraskacode-2015-retrospect/</guid>
      <description>It was a pleasure to attend and speak at Nebraska.Code() this year. The guys in Lincoln are great and really put on a good conference. One of the neat parts of being a speaker is getting to know a lot of other great speakers as you go from one conference to another together. I&#39;ve found that as soon as one conference is over I&#39;m looking forward to the next one and the chance to hang out with the gang.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KCDNUG Last Minute Speaking (or, the perils of running a user group)</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/kcdnug-last-minute-speaking-or-the-perils-of-running-a-user-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2015 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/kcdnug-last-minute-speaking-or-the-perils-of-running-a-user-group/</guid>
      <description>What a crazy user group meeting tonight. Through some schedule mix-ups (partly due to having things scheduled too far in advance and not following up) we ended up with no sponsor and no speaker. I was originally not going to make it to tonight’s meeting due to some schedule conflicts, but they cleared up at the last minute so I joined Brent to help run the meeting. When we go there we discovered that due to schedule conflicts they had we were in a different room, so we got busy redirecting everyone to the new room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xamarin Forms Windows Phone Deployment Tip #1</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/xamarin-forms-windows-phone-deployment-tip-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2015 08:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/xamarin-forms-windows-phone-deployment-tip-1/</guid>
      <description>Here is a helpful tip if you are developing a mobile app using Xamarin Forms and targeting Windows Phone 8.0 (or if you are just writing a WP8.0 Silverlight based app). If you are ready to deploy and filling everything out online it is easier than it first seems. On the Windows Phone Dev Center you will find a helpful link to this article telling you to add some info to the Package.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting your brand’s Twitter timeline in your mobile app</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/getting-your-brands-twitter-timeline-in-your-mobile-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2015 08:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/getting-your-brands-twitter-timeline-in-your-mobile-app/</guid>
      <description>I’m working on a demo app to show some simple functionality that can be done with Xamarin Forms. I’m using the opportunity to also make a business card app for myself (and ultimately for Alien Arc). The app has my picture, name, short bio, and other relevant information. This also seemed like a good place to tie in some of my various social network feeds. I quickly added a page that pulls my blog RSS feed and lists my recent posts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SkillsUSA Coding Competition</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/skillsusa-coding-competition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2015 12:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/skillsusa-coding-competition/</guid>
      <description>On Saturday I had an opportunity to be involved in a SkillsUSA district competition as a judge for the coding competition. I was really impressed with the skill that some of these students (all with less than a year of experience) had. The quality of some of the code they wrote really surprised me.
It was a really enjoyable experience and I was happy to be able to get more involved in the community with the next generation of coders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lessons Learned from My First Speaking Experience</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/lessons-learned-from-my-first-speaking-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2014 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/lessons-learned-from-my-first-speaking-experience/</guid>
      <description>First off, speaking is a rush. It is hard to describe the feeling just after completing a talk. I had to move around, talk to people, see what was going on; it really energized me. I am definitely going to continue to pursue future speaking opportunities as they present themselves, and I’ll keep you posted when they get accepted.

As I mentioned in previous posts, my first talk was on Xamarin Forms, a new technology in a toolset that we are using at Alien Arc, but that is still new to us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why doesn’t my code work in Xamarin.Forms?</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/why-doesnt-my-code-work-in-xamarinforms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2014 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/why-doesnt-my-code-work-in-xamarinforms/</guid>
      <description>If you have tried something in Xamarin.Forms that should work but didn&amp;rsquo;t, don&amp;rsquo;t worry you might not be going crazy (I can&amp;rsquo;t say for sure, I&amp;rsquo;m a programmer, not a psychologist).
I&amp;rsquo;ve been diving deeper into Xamarin.Forms over the last couple months while working on a small project we have as well as in preparation for my upcoming talk at St. Louis Days of .NET. Sometimes in the course of creating a sample project I write some code that I know should work and then watch the exceptions pop-up (or worse, see nothing at all) when I run it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making Progress on Your Small Business Goals</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/making-progress-on-your-small-business-goals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2014 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/making-progress-on-your-small-business-goals/</guid>
      <description>When Brent and I started Alien Arc we had a few basic goals:
 To have more flexible working conditions To be more active with the developer community and conferences To create our own products  We&amp;rsquo;ve done a pretty good job in our first 6 months getting started on some of these goals. We are on-site with our primary client, but they are closer and with the consultant relationship it is much easier to deal with any needs for a flexible schedule.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agile Operations</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/agile-operations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2014 16:04:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/agile-operations/</guid>
      <description>With a new and busy business it is easy to lose track of the little things that need to be done when you are spending every usable minute on billable tasks. This is the challenge we found ourselves faced with a few months into operating Alien Arc.
Enter Aglie We started a Trello board back when we started the business to track tasks like getting our insurance setup and creating a logo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jumping Headfirst Into My First Speaking Engagement</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/jumping-headfirst-into-my-first-speaking-engagement/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2014 15:28:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/jumping-headfirst-into-my-first-speaking-engagement/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been wanting to start speaking at conferences for a while now, but have always been nervous about it. I’ve really wanted to do this for a long time but I specifically remember in 2013 I went to KCDC and was all energized about sharing as a speaker. I decided that I was going to work on having a presentation for the next year. When KCDC 2014 was announced earlier this year I realized I hadn’t even thought about a topic since the week after last years conference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Can Has Pen Input? (or, My first moments with a Surface Pro)</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/i-can-has-pen-input-or-my-first-moments-with-a-surface-pro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2013 08:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/i-can-has-pen-input-or-my-first-moments-with-a-surface-pro/</guid>
      <description>I just picked up my Surface Pro from my local Microsoft Store this morning. I&amp;rsquo;m no stranger to Windows 8; I&amp;rsquo;ve been using it on my desktop since RTM (and a little before) and I bought the RT back on launch day. In general I like the changes that have been made and no longer feel at home on Windows 7. I have especially been digging the way the interface was built around touch with my RT, I think that has helped me accept some of the changes experienced with mouse and keyboard only input.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Processing collections with LINQ using the Aggregate extension method</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/processing-collections-with-linq-using-the-aggregate-extension-method/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2011 22:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/processing-collections-with-linq-using-the-aggregate-extension-method/</guid>
      <description>Everyone knows one of the easiest ways to process collections of objects is using foreach, it is much more elegant and less error prone (IMHO) than using a for (int x..) and looping by index. &amp;nbsp;However, sometimes you get forced into using the indexer to process a collection. &amp;nbsp;This usually happens when you need to look at the current object in context of the previous. &amp;nbsp;
The need to use the indexer and have code like obj[i] == obj[i -1] bugged me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Attaching to external DirectShow graphs using Graph Edit</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/attaching-to-external-directshow-graphs-using-graph-edit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2011 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/attaching-to-external-directshow-graphs-using-graph-edit/</guid>
      <description>In my day job I work on a product that does a lot of video work and in fact has a custom DirectShow player that gets all our video into WPF. &amp;nbsp;It plays multiple files all synchronized (a real challenge).
While looking into ways to improve performance I found myself needing to see how my filter graph was being built. &amp;nbsp;I did a little looking and found that creating an instance of DsROTEntry with a reference to the graph makes it available for external viewing.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>