<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Speaking on Duane Newman</title>
    <link>https://duanenewman.net/categories/speaking/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Speaking on Duane Newman</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright Duane Newman</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 May 2016 15:01:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://duanenewman.net/categories/speaking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Nebraska.Code() 2016</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/nebraska-code-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2016 15:01:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/nebraska-code-2016/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Another &lt;a href=&#34;http://nebraskacode.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Nebraska.Code()&lt;/a&gt; is in the books and it was a real blast. The organizers, Adam &amp;amp; Ken, really put in the effort and run a great conference. The other speakers are always quality company and I really enjoyed meeting a few new ones and getting to know some much better. One of the things I enjoy about conference is the circle of friends you make and meet across the country as you travel to this conference and that conference. We had lots of deep, and many more entertaining conversations.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
      <category>Coding</category>
      
      <category>Community</category>
      
      <category>Deployment</category>
      
      <category>mobile</category>
      
      <category>NCC</category>
      
      <category>NebraskaCode</category>
      
      <category>OSS</category>
      
      <category>Speaking</category>
      
      <category>Xamarin</category>
      
      <category>Xamarin Forms</category>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speaking on DevOps at St. Louis Days of .NET 2015</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/speaking-on-devops-at-st-louis-days-of-net-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2015 09:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/speaking-on-devops-at-st-louis-days-of-net-2015/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&#39;ve been selected to speak at the upcoming St. Louis Days of .NET (STLDODN) on November 12th-14th. I will be presenting my new talk on DevOps, Double Down with DevOps, and am excited about the opportunity to give this topic some attention. &lt;/p&gt;  &lt;h2&gt;Why Speak on DevOps?&lt;/h2&gt;  &lt;p&gt;As a developer I am often frustrated with the amount of manual processes that seem to exist between development and production. Many of us have found ourselves in the situation where we had a single point of failure for a process, the 1 person at the company that knows how to release the new software, or configure the server, or any number of other things that will invariably go wrong when when they are on vacation (or worse, just go on hold). Even if the process is documented or several people know how to do it, you end up with random problems because a step was skipped or some file wasn&#39;t copied.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
      <category>speaking</category>
      
      <category>STLDODN</category>
      
      <category>DevOps</category>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heartland Developers Conference 2015</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/heartland-developers-conference-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2015 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/heartland-developers-conference-2015/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This was my first year speaking at the Heartland Developers Conference in Omaha, although I’ve attended many times through the years as an attendee. The experience was quite a lot of fun, and I had a good time hanging out with old friends and making a few new ones. My wife came with me and good time watching all of us “geeks” hangout. &lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;This was the first time doing a new talk, and the first talk that didn’t involve any demo’s, and it was not scheduled until Friday morning. Needless to say I spent a lot of time fretting about the talk and was constantly tweaking my slides. The talk itself went really well, the audience was very involved with a lot of great questions. My talk was on DevOps and I brought to light the importance and advantages of getting a DevOps friendly environment established. I was happy to see I had a mix of developers, IT guys and managers as I really tried to target the talk to a broad audience. All-in-all I’m looking forward to what HDC might bring next year.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
      <category>agile</category>
      
      <category>DevOps</category>
      
      <category>Community</category>
      
      <category>Speaking</category>
      
      <category>HDC</category>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kansas City Developers Conference 2015 Recap</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/kcdc-2015-recap/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2015 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/kcdc-2015-recap/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In preparation for my fall conference lineup I thought I would take a minute to reflect on this year’s Kansas City Developers Conference. Once again, I am impressed with the quality of conference that the KCDC crew puts together. Kudos go to &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/boontlee&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Boone&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/jonathanfmills&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Jon&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/leebrandt&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Lee&lt;/a&gt; for nurturing a small weekend event into what is, today, one of the top conferences in the Midwest for developers (of any discipline). I’ve had the opportunity to go to some of the “BIG” (and expensive) developer conferences out there and experience what they feel like, and to me KCDC has that same polished feel of conferences that cost 10x as much to attend. It is great to be able to attend a developer conference of that caliber without ever leaving town.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
      <category>Community</category>
      
      <category>speaking</category>
      
      <category>Xamarin</category>
      
      <category>Xamarin Forms</category>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KCDC 2015 Sessions</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/kcdc-2015-sessions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2015 11:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/kcdc-2015-sessions/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;KCDC is just a week away and I&#39;m busy updating my materials. I&#39;m looking forward to meeting some great developers and catching up with what is quickly becoming a close group of speaker friends.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;I&#39;ll be presenting my Xamarin.Forms talk on Thursday morning at 10:10 AM. Conference mornings are always a little rough, but I like getting the talk done early, then I get to relax, network, and enjoy seeing my friends presenting their talks. If you are looking at doing mobile development and have a solid C# background then I encourage you to attend my session.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
      <category>KCDC</category>
      
      <category>speaking</category>
      
      <category>Xamarin</category>
      
      <category>Xamarin Forms</category>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interview with STL Tech Talk at STLDODN 2014</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/interview-with-stl-tech-talk-at-stldodn-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2015 08:23:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/interview-with-stl-tech-talk-at-stldodn-2014/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Back in November 2014 at the &lt;a href=&#34;http://stldodn.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;St. Louis Days of .NET&lt;/a&gt; conference I sat down with JJ Hammond from &lt;a href=&#34;http://stltechtalk.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;STL Tech Talk&lt;/a&gt; for an interview. It was a lot of fun and I had a great time talking about Xamarin, Xamarin.Forms, and mobile development for the C# developer. It got lost somewhere among all the other interview videos, but thanks to Kevin and JJ it is was found and is now posted for your viewing pleasure. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
      <category>Xamarin</category>
      
      <category>Xamarin Forms</category>
      
      <category>STLDODN</category>
      
      <category>Interview</category>
      
      <category>StlTechTalk</category>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nebraska.Code() 2015 Retrospect</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/nebraskacode-2015-retrospect/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2015 09:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/nebraskacode-2015-retrospect/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It was a pleasure to attend and speak at Nebraska.Code() this year. The guys in Lincoln are great and really put on a good conference. One of the neat parts of being a speaker is getting to know a lot of other great speakers as you go from one conference to another together. I&#39;ve found that as soon as one conference is over I&#39;m looking forward to the next one and the chance to hang out with the gang.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
      <category>speaking</category>
      
      <category>Xamarin</category>
      
      <category>Xamarin Forms</category>
      
      <category>Community</category>
      
      <category>mobile</category>
      
      <category>review</category>
      
      <category>NCC</category>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KCDNUG Last Minute Speaking (or, the perils of running a user group)</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/kcdnug-last-minute-speaking-or-the-perils-of-running-a-user-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2015 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/kcdnug-last-minute-speaking-or-the-perils-of-running-a-user-group/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;What a crazy user group meeting tonight. Through some schedule mix-ups (partly due to having things scheduled too far in advance and not following up) we ended up with no sponsor and no speaker.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;I was originally not going to make it to tonight’s meeting due to some schedule conflicts, but they cleared up at the last minute so I joined Brent to help run the meeting. When we go there we discovered that due to schedule conflicts they had we were in a different room, so we got busy redirecting everyone to the new room. After a while we started wondering where the scheduled sponsor was... Then we also started wondering where the speaker was. We soon learned the sponsor didn&#39;t realize they were scheduled for tonight and would not be there, so Brent got on the phone and Alien Arc became the new sponsor. When it was just a few minutes from go-time and still no speaker (didn&#39;t have contact info) it became apparent that one of us was going to speak.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
      <category>speaking</category>
      
      <category>Community</category>
      
      <category>KCDNUG</category>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SkillsUSA Coding Competition</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/skillsusa-coding-competition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2015 12:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/skillsusa-coding-competition/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://duanenewman.net/img/posts/201402-SkillsUSA.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img title=&#34;201402-SkillsUSA&#34; style=&#34;float: right&#34; border=&#34;0&#34; alt=&#34;201402-SkillsUSA&#34; src=&#34;https://duanenewman.net/img/posts/201402-SkillsUSA_thumb.png&#34; width=&#34;244&#34; align=&#34;right&#34; height=&#34;160&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;     &lt;p&gt;On Saturday I had an opportunity to be involved in a SkillsUSA district competition as a judge for the coding competition. I was really impressed with the skill that some of these students (all with less than a year of experience) had. The quality of some of the code they wrote really surprised me.&lt;/p&gt;    &lt;p&gt;It was a really enjoyable experience and I was happy to be able to get more involved in the community with the next generation of coders. I look forward to other opportunities to work with the future of software development and technology.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
      <category>Technology</category>
      
      <category>SkillsUSA</category>
      
      <category>Judging</category>
      
      <category>Coding</category>
      
      <category>Community</category>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lessons Learned from My First Speaking Experience</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/lessons-learned-from-my-first-speaking-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2014 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/lessons-learned-from-my-first-speaking-experience/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;First off, speaking is a rush. It is hard to describe the feeling just after completing a talk. I had to move around, talk to people, see what was going on; it really energized me. I am definitely going to continue to pursue future speaking opportunities as they present themselves, and I’ll keep you posted when they get accepted.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://duanenewman.net/img/posts/OS7A6321_1.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img title=&#34;OS7A6321&#34; style=&#34;border-left-width: 0px; max-width: 100%; height: auto; border-right-width: 0px; width: 100%; background-image: none; border-bottom-width: 0px; float: none; padding-top: 0px; padding-left: 0px; margin-left: auto; display: block; padding-right: 0px; border-top-width: 0px; margin-right: auto&#34; border=&#34;0&#34; alt=&#34;OS7A6321&#34; src=&#34;https://duanenewman.net/img/posts/OS7A6321_thumb_1.jpg&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
      <category>Xamarin</category>
      
      <category>Xamarin Forms</category>
      
      <category>tips</category>
      
      <category>speaking</category>
      
      <category>STLDODN</category>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jumping Headfirst Into My First Speaking Engagement</title>
      <link>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/jumping-headfirst-into-my-first-speaking-engagement/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2014 15:28:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duanenewman.net/blog/post/jumping-headfirst-into-my-first-speaking-engagement/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I’ve been wanting to start speaking at conferences for a while now, but have always been nervous about it. I’ve really wanted to do this for a long time but I specifically remember in 2013 I went to KCDC and was all energized about sharing as a speaker. I decided that I was going to work on having a presentation for the next year. When KCDC 2014 was announced earlier this year I realized I hadn’t even thought about a topic since the week after last years conference. I was a little bummed by my lack of effort, to say the least.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
      <category>STLDODN</category>
      
      <category>Xamarin</category>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>